

Mr. Vaibhav Bhagwan Kashyap.

Civil/Environment Engineer/GIS Professional

- 💡 1754, Plot No 02, Jayram Colony, East of Holy Family Convent Highschool, Vidyanagar. Karad. Dist Satara. Maharashtra. India, 415124 Karad, India
 - vaibhavkashyap1690@gmail.com

 √ 7350402109

 16/03/1990

 Indian

 Unmarried

 Unmarried

 Indian

 Value

 Val

in Vaibhav Kashyap

PROFILE

Hello! I am Vaibhav Bhagwan Kashyap from Karad, Dist Satara, Maharashtra. I have completed my degree in Civil Engineering from Solapur University with a CGPA of 8.25. Now I am pursuing my M.Tech in Environmental Science and Technolgy, from Shivaji University, Kolhapur. Also, I am Pursuing GIS and Remote Sensing Diploma from Karad itself. I have worked as a site engineer for about 1year and after that, I had been working as a prof in Civil Dept, at R.N.P.C.Indoli, Karad for about 3years. Now I have been working on projects with GIS for about 6months. Also addon to it I am in process of implying REMOTE SENSING knowledge to my Knowledge cart.

EDUCATION		
01/2022 – present	Diploma In Geo Informatics, AGT's Geo Spatial Technology. Karad. Maharashtra	Karad, India
06/2020 – present	M.Tech (Environmental Science & Technology), Shivaji University, Kolhapur. Maharashtra	Kolhapur, India
07/2014 - 06/2018	B.E. Civil, J.S.P.M's Bhagwant Institute of Technology, Barshi. Maharashtra	Barshi, Dist. Solapur, India
06/2005 – 06/2007	H.S.C, Yashwantrao Chavan College of Science. Karad	Karad, India
06/1994 – 06/2005	S.S.C, Holy Family Convent Highschool, Vidyanagar. Karad. Maharashtra	Karad, India
COURSES		
01/2021 – present	Diploma In Geo Informatics, <i>AGT's Geo Spatial Technology. Karad</i> GIS, ArcGIS 10.8, AutoCAD mapping, Revit Mapping, Remote Sensing.	Karad, India

12/2021 – 01/2022	AutoDesk Revit Architecture + Vray, Ajnkya CADD SOLUTIONS This is to certify that Mr. Vaibhav Bhagwan Kashyap Has successfully completed his course in Autodesk Revit Architecture 2019 with an Grade A+	Karad, India
05/2017 - 07/2017	Auto CAD 2D, First Step Infotech, Datapro This is to Certify that Mr. Vaibhav Bhagwan Kashyap, has successfully completed his "AUTOCAD(1 Month) and passed the exam held with an A+ grade.	Karad, India

SKILLS

ArcGIS 10.8 (GIS-based software for Mapping, creating Layers, Large Databases. Handon experience in ArcGIS software),

AutoDesk Revit Architechture (Revit Architecture Civil Modelling and designing Software for Architectural Drawings. Along with Vray To get smooth and high-quality rendered images.),

AutoDesk AutoCAD 2D Drafting (Preparation of Submission drawings along with standard Business Building planning and design. eg: Beam And Column layout plan, Sectional view plans, Elevation, Etc.),

Remote Sensing (Beginner and a student at remote sensing learning new techniques to simplify and use these field in civil applications)

	LANGUAGES	
English	● ● ● ● Hindi	• • • • •
Marathi	• • • •	
	PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE	
06/2018 – 06/2021	Lecturer at Civil Engineering Department, Ramrao Nikam Polytechnic College, Indoli. Karad	Karad, India
2017 - 2018	Site Engineer(Training), Jadhav Construction Firm, Barshi. Maharashtra	Barshi, India
PUBLICATIONS		
08/04/2021	BASIC CIVIL ENGINEERING. ADVANCED SURVEYING – THEORY NOTES: AUTHOR – VAIBHAV B KASHYAP [B.E (CIVIL), M.TECH (ENVIRONMENTAL SCIENCE & TECHNOLOGY)], Kindle Edition	
07/04/2021	BASIC CIVIL ENGINEERING.: SURVEYING – THEORY NOTES. By, Vaibh Kindle Edition	av B Kashyap,
06/04/2021	Vastu-Shastra Basics: Mr. Vaibhav B Kashyap B.E Civil, M. Tech (EST) Kindle Edition ☑	,
14/04/2021	Estimation and Professional Practices - Civil Engineers Guide: Autho Kashyap B.E Civil, M.Tech (Environmental Science & Technology), Ki	

11/04/2021	Design Of Steel Structures - DSS: AUTHOR - VAIBHAV B KASHYAP [B.E (CIVIL), M.TECH (ENVIRONMENTAL SCIENCE & TECHNOLOGY)], Kindle Edition ☑
20/11/2021	ARITHMETIC AND PRINCIPLES OF MEASUREMENT: Series of Estimating & Costing. By, Vaibhav B Kashyap, Kindle Edition ☑
17/11/2021	MEASURING EXCAVATION AND SITEWORK: E-Book by, Vaibhav B Kashyap., Kindle Edition ☑
21/06/2020	STATIC PUSHOVER ANALYSIS FOR KOYNA DAM, IJSR Paper I'd: SR20430182234
16/09/2019	IMPROVING SOLID WASTE MANAGEMENT FOR BARSHI CITY, IJSR Paper I'd: ART 20201312
20/10/2019	ZERO ENERGY BUILDINGS - A Critical Look At The Definition., IJRESM

INTERESTS

• GIS & Remote Sensing

• Civil Engineer

• Environmental Engineer

 Revit Architecture Planning, Designing and Modelling

CERTIFICATES

Diploma In Geo Informatics

ArcGIS and Remote Sensing

TEACHERS IINOVATION AWARD - Zero Investment

Innovation For Education Initiatives

Infinity Engineering Training center

Two Days Workshop on - Civil Engineering to Civil

Engineering Industries.

National Network Security Championship

Auto Desk Revit Architecture + Vray

Autodesk AutoCAD 2D

One Week Faculty Development Program organized by MSBTE from 21st to 25th January 2020

	PROJECTS
03/2021 - 07/2022	Analysis of Landslide Hazard Zones Using GIS & Remote Sensing in Western Ghat (Chandoli region), Maharashtra, Project On Field Guide: Mr. Suhas Shedge Sir. AGT Geospatial Technology, Karad. Project Guide(University): Mr. S.M.Bhosale Sir. H.O.D. Env. SCi & Tech, DOT. Kolhapur. Project Co-Guide(University): Dr. J.D.Patil Sir. DOT. Kolhapur.
02/2022 – 03/2022	Taxation Project Using GIS For Bhambe Grampanchayat, Tal. Karad. Maharashtra. India, Project Guide: Mr. Suhas Shedge Sir. AGT Geospatial Technology, Karad

Working of Effluent Treatment Plant At Sahyadri Sah. Sakhar Karkhana. Ltd. Karad, WOrking and Principle working of ETP at SUGAR INDUSTRY. Sahyadri Sahakari Sakhar Karkahna. Ltd. Yashwantnagar. Karad
Static Pushover Analysis Of Koyna Dam, A Literature Review based Study Project
Pavement Blocks From Solid Waste(LDPE & HDPE Strands), Making of Paving blocks from Plastic waste Found in Municipal waste
Improvement in Solid Waste Management, <i>Improvement in Solid Waste Management.</i>
AWARDS
International Conference on Advances in civil and Structural Engineering, Government College of Engineering, Karad
TEACHERS IINOVATION AWARD - Zero Investment Innovation For Education Initiatives, <i>Sri Aurobindo Society, ZIIEI.</i>
State Basketball at Osmanabad Maharashtra 2016-17, State Sports Authority
National Basketball at Vadodara Gujarat 2016-17, National Sports Authority

REFERENCES

Mr. Suhas Shedge, *GIS and Remote Sensing Expert*, AGT's Geo Spatial Technology, karad agt.tarale@gmail.com, 9372222793

Mr. Akshay Kulkarni, *Civil Design Engineer*, Vishwakarma Construction Karad akahaykulkarni93@gmail.com, 9834848557

Mr.Santosh Kamble, *Lecturer at Basic English Department*, Ramrao Nikam Polytechnic College Indoli, Karad santoshkamble5217@gmail.com, 87882 97512

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned information is correct up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars.

Mr. Vaibhav Bhagwan Kashyap

Karad